Guide to the Stevens family papers, [ca. 1775-2010]
Stevens family papers, [ca. 1775-2010]
- Series II. Robert (Wadleigh) Smith Stevens Generation
  - II-B. Robert (Wadleigh) Smith Stevens (1824-1893)
    - Personal Papers
      - Diary & School notebook*Scans and transcripts from this item available online: various entries from July 4th through November 23rd, 1835, 1835, 1835 (Box 1, Folder 45)
      - Diary/Journal*Scans and transcripts from this item available online: entries from October 25th through 27th, 1841; list of ladies at end of journal.**Full transcript of journal available online., 1841-1845 (Box 1, Folder 46)
      - Correspondence, 1836-1873, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 44)
      - Correspondence, Jan-June 1870 (Box 59, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence, July-Dec 1870 (Box 59, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence, 1871 (Box 59, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence, 1872 (Box 59, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence, 1873 (Box 59, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence (and transcripts), Jan-June 1874 (Box 61, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence (and transcripts), July-Nov 1874 (Box 61, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence (and transcripts), December 1874 (Box 61, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence (and transcripts), December 1874 (Box 61, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence (and transcripts), Jan-June 1875 (Box 61, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence (and transcripts), Sept-Dec 1875 (Box 61, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence (and transcripts), Jan-June 1876 (Box 61, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence (and transcripts), July-Dec 1876 (Box 61, Folder 8)
      - Diary, 1885 (Box 1, Folder 46)
      - Estate papers: Daybook "Journal A", 1893-1896 (Box 1, Folder 47)
      - Estate papers: Daybook "Journal B", 1896-1899 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      - Estate papers: Daybook "Journal C", 1899-1903 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      - Estate papers: Daybook "Journal D", 1904-1908 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      - Estate papers: Daybook "Journal E", 1908-1912 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      - Estate papers: Account book "Ledger A", 1893-1898 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      - Estate papers: Account book "Ledger B", 1899-1904 (Box 2, Folder 6)
      - Estate papers: Account book "Ledger C", 1905-1912 (Box 2, Folder 7)
      - Estate papers: Account balance book, 1893-1898 (Box 27, Folder -)
      - Estate papers: Account balance book, 1899-1911 (Box 27, Folder -)
      - Estate papers: Tax receipts, 1893-1915 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      - Newspaper clippings and articles, 1857-1893, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 2)
      - Miscellaneous: Book plates, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 3)
      - Miscellaneous: Menu cards (2), 1884, 1893 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Business Correspondence (non-railroad)
      - Correspondence, 1847-1857 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence: Copybook "From R.S.S.", 1850-1856 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence: Copybook "From R.S.S.", 1858-1860 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence, 1858 (Box 3, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence, Jan-Nov 1859 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence, Dec.1-17, 1859 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence, Dec.18-31, 1859 (Box 3, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence, Jan.1-10, 1860 (Box 3, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence, Jan.11-20, 1860 (Box 3, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence, Jan.21-31, 1860 (Box 3, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence, Feb.1-10, 1860 (Box 3, Folder 9)
      - Correspondence, Feb.11-17, 1860 (Box 3, Folder 10)
      - Correspondence, Feb.18-23, 1860 (Box 3, Folder 11)
      - Correspondence, Feb.24-29, 1860 (Box 3, Folder 12)
      - Correspondence, Mar.1-6, 1860 (Box 3, Folder 13)
      - Correspondence, Mar.7-13, 1860 (Box 3, Folder 14)
      - Correspondence, Mar.14-21, 1860 (Box 3, Folder 15)
      - Correspondence, Mar.22-31, 1860 (Box 3, Folder 16)
      - Correspondence, Apr.1-7, 1860 (Box 3, Folder 17)
      - Correspondence, Apr.8-16, 1860 (Box 3, Folder 18)
      - Correspondence, Apr.17-30, 1860 (Box 3, Folder 19)
      - Correspondence, May 1-17, 1860 (Box 3, Folder 20)
      - Correspondence, May 18-31, 1860 (Box 3, Folder 21)
      - Correspondence, June-Sep 1860 (Box 3, Folder 22)
      - Correspondence, Oct 1860-Jan 1861 (Box 3, Folder 23)
      - Correspondence, Feb 1861 (Box 3, Folder 24)
      - Correspondence, March-Dec 1861 (Box 3, Folder 25)
      - Correspondence, Jan-July 1862 (Box 3, Folder 26)
      - Correspondence, Aug 1862-1864 (Box 3, Folder 27)
      - Correspondence, Jan.1-9, 1865 (Box 3, Folder 28)
      - Correspondence, Jan.10-27, 1865 (Box 3, Folder 29)
      - Correspondence, Jan.28-31, 1865 (Box 3, Folder 30)
      - Correspondence, Feb 1865 (Box 3, Folder 31)
      - Telegram book, 1870 (Box 60, Folder -)
      - Correspondence, 1869-July 1886 (Box 3, Folder 32)
      - Correspondence, Oct 1886-March 1888 (Box 3, Folder 33)
      - Correspondence, April 1888-July 1889 (Box 3, Folder 34)
      - Correspondence, August 1889-March 1890 (Box 3, Folder 35)
      - Correspondence, April 1890-March 1891 (Box 3, Folder 36)
      - Correspondence, April 1891-June 1891 (Box 3, Folder 37)
      - Correspondence, July 1891 (Box 3, Folder 38)
      - Correspondence, Aug 1891-1894, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 39)
      - Correspondence: "C.F. Stone - Peabody, Kansas" (Holstein Freisian cattle), 1889-1893 (Box 3, Folder 40)
      - Correspondence: "Colorado Mining Property", 1880-April 1881 (Box 3, Folder 41)
      - Correspondence: "Colorado Mining Property", July 1881-1882 (Box 3, Folder 42)
      - Correspondence: "Colorado Mining Property", 1883-1887 (Box 3, Folder 43)
      - Correspondence: "Colorado Mining Property", 1888-1893 (Box 3, Folder 44)
      - Correspondence: "Colorado Mining Property" - Mine and company descriptions, maps, n.d. (ca.1880s) (Box 3, Folder 45)
      - Correspondence: "First National Bank", May 1889 (Box 3, Folder 46)
      - Correspondence: "G.M. Munger - Eureka" (Holstein Freisian cattle), 1890 (Box 3, Folder 47)
      - Correspondence: Broadside removed from "G.M. Munger - Eureka" folder (3-47), 1892 (Box 76, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence: "L.W. Thayer & C.L. Arnold - Political", 1885-1886 (Box 3, Folder 48)
      - Correspondence: Mille Lac Indians (+OS map), 1876-1884 (Box 3, Folder 49)
      - Correspondence: Map of the Land Department, St. Paul & Duluth R.R. Co, removed from the "Mille Lac Indians" file 3-49 (Box 76, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence: "Schell Lands" (includes tax receipts), 1883-1894 (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - Business Papers (non-railroad)
      - Certificates (professional), 1844-1868 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      - Contracts: Deeds, insurance, leases, mortgages, 1840-1885 (Box 3, Folder 51)
      - Contracts: Deeds, insurance, leases, mortgages, 1886-1890, 1899 (Box 3, Folder 52)
      - Abstract of title: Osage County, Kansas, 1889 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      - Stocks: Companies A-P, 1880-1882 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - Stocks: Companies S-Z, 1880-1882 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - Lease files, 1888 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      - Lease files, 1889-1890 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - Mortgage/loan files (1 of 4), 1885-1892 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - Mortgage/loan files (2 of 4), 1883-1891 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - Mortgage/loan files (3 of 4), 1886-1892 (Box 4, Folder 9)
      - Mortgage/loan files (4 of 4), 1886-1891 (Box 4, Folder 10)
      - Mortgage book: Kansas land, 1880-1889 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - Mortgage book: Kansas land, 1884-1891 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - Mortgage book/Tax book: Kansas land, 1886-1893 (Box 4, Folder 11)
      - Mortgage book: Kansas land, 1893-1908 (Box 4, Folder 12)
      - Lot book: Descriptions and maps of lots of land in Osage and Coffey Counties, KS (Box 4, Folder 13)
      - Lot book: List of lots, owners, buyers, and prices (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Land lists and descriptions, 1860-1895, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 10)
      - Land maps and mortgages: Osage County, 1889-1891 (Box 5, Folder 11)
      - Land maps and mortgages: Osage C ounty (Box 76, Folder 6)
      - Loan book: "Note Register A", 1883-1899 (Box 30, Folder -)
      - Account book: Indian housing - "The Great Book", 1861-1862 (Box 4, Folder 14)
      - Account book: Indian housing, 1861-1862 (Box 4, Folder 15)
      - Account book "A": Office of R.S. Stevens, 1886-1893 (Box 31, Folder -)
      - Account balance book, 1886-1893 (Box 27, Folder -)
      - Accounts/Notes with G.A. Colton, 1871-1880 (Box 5, Folder 12)
      - Daybook: Office of R.S. Stevens - "Journal" (A?), 1886-1891 (Box 27, Folder -)
      - Daybook: Office of R.S. Stevens - "Journal B", 1892-1893 (Box 30, Folder -)
      - Tax receipts, 1870-1876 (Box 5, Folder 13)
      - Tax receipts, 1877-1890 (Box 5, Folder 14)
      - Tax receipts: "Missouri Land", 1884-1904 (Box 5, Folder 15)
      - Receipts, bills, statements, promissory notes, 1860-1893 (Box 5, Folder 16)
      - Financial statement: Schell Town Co., March 12, 1875 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      - Flyers & broadsides (reg. Kansas land), 1868-1895, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 16)
      - Deposition: Caleb B. Smith, Secretary of the Interior of the United States (copy), May 7, 1862 (Box 5, Folder 18)
      - Congressional bills, 1884-1885 (Box 4, Folder 17)
      - Congressional proceedings and debates (copies), 1884-1885 (Box 4, Folder 18)
      - Testimony of Sarah Winnemucca to the Indian Affairs Committee (RWSS was Chairman), April 22, 1884 (Box 70, Folder -)
      - Autograph book - U.S. Congress, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 19)
      - Election stickers: "For Representative in Congress, Robert S. Stevens", n.d. (Box 4, Folder 20)
      - Event tickets and passes, 1884-1885, 1894 (Box 4, Folder 20)
      - Notebook: Alphabetical and subject lists (Box 4, Folder 21)
      - Miscellaneous: Great American Tea Company ephemera, 1871 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Railroad Papers
      - Broadside: Tonowanda Railroad Company, one page unsigned subscription form to the railroad. RWSS owned bonds in this road., 1832 (Box 76, Folder 3)
      - Outgoing correspondence. Letterbook I, 499 pp. plus name index, Nov. 1, 1870-Mar. 9, 1875 (Box 51, Folder -)
      - Outgoing correspondence. Letterbook II, 492 pp. plus name index, Jan. 29, 1872-July 25, 1873 (Box 52, Folder -)
      - Outgoing correspondence. Letterbook III, "Private Official," 494 pp. plus name index, July 30, 1873-Dec. 18, 1874 (Box 53, Folder -)
      - Outgoing correspondence. Letterbook IV, "R.S. Stevens," 489 pp. plus name index, Aug. 23, 1875-Oct. 4, 1875 (Box 54, Folder -)
      - Outgoing correspondence. Letterbook V, 698 pp. plus name index, Aug. 20, 1875-Sep. 30, 1876 (Box 55, Folder -)
      - From bound volume of correspondence labelled "To RSS 1874:" - petition from voters of Madison Twp, Mo. (& transcript), 1870 (Box 59, Folder 1)
      - From bound volume - correspondence from Levi Parsons (& transcript), 1871 (Box 59, Folder 4)
      - From bound volume - correspondence from J. W. Fuller (& transcript), April 5, 1872 (Box 59, Folder 6)
      - From bound volume - notice from R. S. Stevens to employees of Missouri-Kansas-Texas Railway (& transcript), Oct. 27, 1873 (Box 59, Folder 9)
      - From bound volume - incoming correspondence, September 1874 (Box 59, Folder 10)
      - From bound volume - incoming correspondence, November 1874 (Box 59, Folder 11)
      - From bound volume - incoming correspondence, December 1874 (Box 59, Folder 12)
      - Name index, 1875 (Box 56, Folder 1)
      - Incoming correspondence, July 1875 (Box 56, Folder 2)
      - Incoming correspondence, July 1875 (Box 57, Folder 1)
      - Incoming correspondence, August 1875 (Box 56, Folder 3)
      - Incoming correspondence*Scans and transcripts from this folder available online: Letters of August 19th and August 21st, 1875, August 1875 (Box 56, Folder 4)
      - Incoming correspondence, August 1875 (Box 56, Folder 5)
      - Incoming correspondence, August 1875 (Box 57, Folder 2)
      - Incoming correspondence, August 1875 (Box 57, Folder 3)
      - Incoming correspondence, August 1875 (Box 57, Folder 4)
      - Incoming correspondence, September 1875 (Box 56, Folder 6)
      - Incoming correspondence, September 1875 (Box 56, Folder 7)
      - Incoming correspondence, September 1875 (Box 56, Folder 8)
      - Incoming correspondence, September 1875 (Box 56, Folder 9)
      - Incoming correspondence, September 1875 (Box 57, Folder 5)
      - Incoming correspondence, October 1875 (Box 56, Folder 10)
      - Incoming correspondence, October 1875 (Box 56, Folder 11)
      - Incoming correspondence, October 1875 (Box 56, Folder 12)
      - Incoming correspondence, October 1875 (Box 56, Folder 13)
      - Incoming correspondence, October 1875 (Box 56, Folder 14)
      - Incoming correspondence, October 1875 (Box 56, Folder 15)
      - Incoming correspondence, October 1875 (Box 56, Folder 16)
      - Incoming correspondence, October 1875 (Box 56, Folder 17)
      - Incoming correspondence, October 1875 (Box 56, Folder 18)
      - Incoming correspondence, October 1875 (Box 56, Folder 19)
      - Incoming correspondence, October 1875 (Box 56, Folder 20)
      - Incoming correspondence, October 1875 (Box 56, Folder 21)
      - Incoming correspondence, October 1875 (Box 56, Folder 22)
      - Incoming correspondence, October 1875 (Box 57, Folder 6)
      - Incoming correspondence, October 1875 (Box 57, Folder 7)
      - Incoming correspondence, November 1875 (Box 56, Folder 23)
      - Incoming correspondence, November 1875 (Box 56, Folder 24)
      - Incoming correspondence, November 1875 (Box 56, Folder 25)
      - Incoming correspondence, November 1875 (Box 56, Folder 26)
      - Incoming correspondence, November 1875 (Box 57, Folder 8)
      - Incoming correspondence, November 1875 (Box 57, Folder 9)
      - Incoming correspondence, December 1875 (Box 56, Folder 27)
      - Incoming correspondence, December 1875 (Box 56, Folder 28)
      - Incoming correspondence, December 1875 (Box 56, Folder 29)
      - Incoming correspondence, December 1875 (Box 56, Folder 30)
      - Incoming correspondence, December 1875 (Box 56, Folder 31)
      - Incoming correspondence, December 1875 (Box 56, Folder 32)
      - Incoming correspondence, December 1875 (Box 56, Folder 33)
      - Incoming correspondence, December 1875 (Box 57, Folder 10)
      - Incoming correspondence, December 1875 (Box 57, Folder 11)
      - Incoming correspondence, January 1876 (Box 57, Folder 12)
      - Incoming correspondence, January 1876 (Box 57, Folder 13)
      - Incoming correspondence, February 1876 (Box 57, Folder 14)
      - Incoming correspondence, February 1876 (Box 57, Folder 15)
      - Incoming correspondence, March 1876 (Box 57, Folder 16)
      - Incoming correspondence, March 1876 (Box 57, Folder 17)
      - Incoming correspondence, April 1876 (Box 57, Folder 18)
      - Incoming correspondence, April 1876 (Box 57, Folder 19)
      - Incoming correspondence, April 1876 (Box 57, Folder 20)
      - Incoming correspondence, May 1876 (Box 57, Folder 21)
      - Incoming correspondence. Bound volume of letters I, Aug 1875-Jan 1876 (Box 58, Folder -)
      - Incoming correspondence. Bound volume of letters II, 489 pp. plus name index, Feb-Dec 1876 (Box 58, Folder -)
      - Other correspondence, Jan-June 1870 (Box 59, Folder 2)
      - Other correspondence, July-Dec 1870 (Box 59, Folder 3)
      - Other correspondence, 1871 (Box 59, Folder 5)
      - Other correspondence, 1872 (Box 59, Folder 7)
      - Other correspondence, 1873 (Box 59, Folder 8)
      - Bills, receipts, statements (copybook): Hannibal & St. Joseph Railroad Co., 1876-1877 (Box 25, Folder 6)
      - Railway miscellany: Railway passes, n.d. (Box 62, Folder -)
      - Railway miscellany: Missouri, Kansas, and Texas Railway Company, 1871 (Box 62, Folder -)
      - Map: Land Department, St. Paul & Duluth R.R. Co. (scouting land in the Mille Lac Reservation) (Box 76, Folder 5)
      - Maps (Box 13R(63), Folder -)
      - Photographs (Box 13R(63), Folder -)
      - Book of photographs: Locomotive Repair Shops, Parsons Kansas, Missouri Kansas and Texas Railway Company, 1907 (Box 72, Folder 1)
      - 13 large photos of the construction of the MK & T Railroad, n.d. (Box 72, Folder -)
      - Booklet: "General Description of the Locomotives - MK & T Rwy." A listing and description of all locomotives owned by the MK & T from inception to June, 1890 (Box 75, Folder 1)
      - A small leather-bound book marked "A.L. & L.O. R.R., Topography No. 3 - Earth Quantities." A survey notebook done for a railroad, with drawings in the front showing the route, and in the rear are the cut and fill requirements. (Box 75, Folder 2)
      - Maps of the K.C. & P. Railroad, n.d. (Box 75, Folder 3)
      - Railway miscellany: "A Man Unacquainted With The Geography..." newspaper article, n.d. (Box 75, Folder 4)
      - R. W. S. Stevens' salary paid to himself, 1875 (Box 75, Folder 5)
      - Leather-bound pamphlet: "Statistics, H. & St. Jo. R. R. Co., R. S. Stevens", 1872-76 (Box 76, Folder 1)
      - Misc. railroad documents, 1888 (Box 76, Folder 2)
      - Scrapbook: Hannibal & St. Joseph Railroad Co., 1877-1878 (Box 77, Folder -)
      - Newspaper: The Parsons Sun: Katy Special, 23-May-70 (Box 26, Folder -)
      - Newspaper: The Denison Herald - "Katy M-K-T Railroad At the End of the Line" (2 copies), Dec.13, 1987 (Box 26, Folder -)
  - II-C. Mary Proctor (Smith) Stevens (1828-1917)
    - Correspondence received, 1851-1854 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence received, 1855-1869 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence received, 1870-1878 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence received, 1879-1914 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence received (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence written, 1838-1862 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Poetry, 1839-1860, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - A Keepsake, 1844 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Invitations, 1874-1914, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Calling cards, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Ephemera & miscellaneous notes, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Wooden box which held the calling cards, invitations, and ephemera (Box 50, Folder -)
  - II-D. Albert Clark Stevens (1854-1919)
    - Personal Papers
      - Correspondence received, 1869-Jan.1903 (Box 4, Folder 31)
      - Correspondence received, Feb.1903-1906, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 32)
      - Correspondence written, 1904-1919, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 33)
      - School papers, 1866-1873 (Box 5, Folder 21)
      - School scrapbook, 1872-1874 (Box 4, Folder 34)
      - School ephemera, 1872-1906 (Box 4, Folder 35)
      - Athletics ephemera and memorabilia, 1874-1892 (Box 4, Folder 36 (+Cons))
      - Pencil and ink sketches, 1870s, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 37)
      - Biographies, genealogies, business/calling cards, signatures, license as a lay reader, poem (Box 4, Folder 38 (+Cons))
      - Wedding papers, 1903 (Box 4, Folder 39)
      - Obituaries & estate papers, 1902, 1919 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Business Papers
      - Correspondence, 1874-1919, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - Patents & Copyrights, 1877-1904, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - Publications - "Moonshine", 1874 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Publications - Phrenology article and research, 1874 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - Publications - "A Record of Progress" and "Interviewing a King", 1903, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - Publications - Cyclopedia of Fraternities submissions and notes, pub. 1909 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      - Business newspaper clippings and publication advertisements, 1892-1972 (Box 6, Folder 8 (+Cons))
      - Newspaper clippings and publication advertisements, 1909, 1915, 1916 (Box 76, Folder 7)
      - Scrapbook of his articles, 1874-1894 (Box 29, Folder -)
      - St. James Hotel register page, 1879 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Fraternal Organizations
      - Correspondence, 1893-1917 (Box 6, Folder 10(+Cons))
      - Minutes. Ivanhoe Lodge, No.88 F. & A.M., 1901 (Box 6, Folder 10)
      - Ephemera, 1900-1928 (Box 6, Folder 11)
      - Newspaper Clippings, 1896-1897, 1917 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - II-E. Cora Caroline (Stevens) Reynolds (1856-1936)
    - Correspondence, 1868-Jan 1870 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, Jan-Feb 1870 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, July 1872 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, Aug 1872 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, 1873 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, 1874 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, 1875 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, 1878-1880 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, Feb-March 1881 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence (includes letters to Anna Hasting Stevens), April 1881 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, May 1882-1890 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Scrapbook (regarding her husband, John H. Reynolds), 1878-1927 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Series III. Frederick Charles Stevens Generation
  - III-A. Frederick Charles Stevens (formerly Charles Frederick) (1856-1916)
    - Business Correspondence
      - Correspondence: Washington & Georgetown Railroad Co., 1894 (Box 5, Folder 22)
      - Correspondence, 1902-Jan.16, 1903 (Box 5, Folder 23)
      - Correspondence, Jan.20-31, 1903 (Box 5, Folder 24)
      - Correspondence, Feb.2-19, 1903 (Box 5, Folder 25)
      - Correspondence, Feb.20-25, 1903 (Box 5, Folder 26)
      - Correspondence, Feb.26-18, 1903 (Box 5, Folder 27)
      - Correspondence, Mar.1-4, 1903 (Box 5, Folder 28)
      - Correspondence, Mar.5-9, 1903 (Box 5, Folder 29)
      - Correspondence, Mar.10-11, 1903 (Box 5, Folder 30)
      - Correspondence, Mar.12-13, 1903 (Box 5, Folder 31)
      - Correspondence, Mar.14-16, 1903 (Box 5, Folder 32)
      - Correspondence, Mar.17-18, 1903 (Box 5, Folder 33)
      - Correspondence, Mar.19, 1903 (Box 5, Folder 34)
      - Correspondence, Mar.20-23, 1903 (Box 5, Folder 35)
      - Correspondence, Mar.24-25, 1903 (Box 5, Folder 36)
      - Correspondence, Mar.26, 1903 (Box 5, Folder 37)
      - Correspondence, Mar.27-31, 1903 (Box 5, Folder 38)
      - Correspondence, Apr.1-3, 1903 (Box 5, Folder 39)
      - Correspondence, Apr.4-7, 1903 (Box 5, Folder 40)
      - Correspondence, Apr.8-9, 1903 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence, Apr.10-14, 1903 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence, Apr.15-17. 1903 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence, Apr.18-21, 1903 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence, Apr.22-23, 1903 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence, Apr.24-29, 1903 (Box 7, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence: Enclosure from Bigelow, Kennard & Co. letter to Everett & Mead, 29-Apr-03 (Box 76, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence, Apr.30-May 6, 1903 (Box 7, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence, May 7-30, 1903 (Box 7, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence, Jun.1-5, 1903 (Box 7, Folder 9)
      - Correspondence, Jun.6-Jul.9, 1903 (Box 7, Folder 10)
      - Correspondence, Jul.10-31, 1903 (Box 7, Folder 11)
      - Correspondence, Aug-03 (Box 7, Folder 12)
      - Correspondence, Sep.1-22, 1903 (Box 7, Folder 13)
      - Correspondence, Sep.24-Nov.6, 1903 (Box 7, Folder 14)
      - Correspondence, Nov.11-Dec.6, 1903 (Box 7, Folder 15)
      - Correspondence, Dec.7-11, 1903 (Box 7, Folder 16)
      - Correspondence, Dec.14, 1903-Jan.2, 1904 (Box 7, Folder 17)
      - Correspondence: Copybook, with index, Jan.30, 1905-Jan.16 1907 (Box 7, Folder 18)
      - Correspondence: Copybook "5," with index, Aug.23, 1907-Oct.11, 1907 (Box 7, Folder 19)
      - Correspondence: Copybook "6," with index, Oct.11, 1907-Dec.17, 1907 (Box 7, Folder 20)
      - Correspondence: Copybook "2," with index, Dec.17, 1907-Feb.13, 1908 (Box 6, Folder 24)
      - Correspondence: Copybook "8," with index, Feb.13, 1908-March 25, 1908 (Box 6, Folder 25)
      - Correspondence: Copybook "9," with index, March 25, 1908-May 6, 1908 (Box 6, Folder 26)
      - Correspondence: Copybook "10", May 6, 1908-July 31, 1908 (Box 6, Folder 27)
      - Correspondence: Copybook "11," with index, July 31, 1908-Sep.30, 1908 (Box 6, Folder 28)
      - Correspondence: Copybook "12," with index, Oct.1, 1908-Dec.12, 1908 (Box 6, Folder 29)
      - Correspondence: Copybook "13," with index, Dec.12, 1908-Feb.2, 1909 (Box 6, Folder 30)